<rules>
	<rule punish="Deathmatching">
		Deathmatching is not allowed outside the city of Las Venturas. Criminals are allowed to attack Law agents IF they are wanted and being chased by them. 
		Also, killing other players in ANY interior is not allowed, even if it's in Las Venturas;
	</rule>
	
	<rule punish="Cheating">
		The use of trainers and bugs is strictly forbidden and will result in a ban from the server;
	</rule>
	
	<rule punish="Insulting\Flaming">
		Heavy insulting and being racist towards other players will result in a permanent server ban;
		<info>Only offensive flame is forbidden;</info>
		<info>Insulting any religion is forbidden as well;</info>
		<info>We have zero tolerance to racism;</info>
	</rule>	
	<rule punish="Annoying staff">
		Annoying the Server Staff is not allowed and will result in a punishment;
		<info>Don't PM admins requesting for removing Slaps, Freezes, reconnects and kicks, we wont delete it;</info>
		<info>Don't use Support or SMS admins for Events cause it will only result in a mute;</info>
		<info>Requesting unfair advantages will result in a mute;</info>
	</rule>	
	<rule punish="Avoiding punishments">
		Any attempt to avoid punishment by the server staff will only result in a larger punishment to be applied;
	</rule>	
	<rule punish="Advertising">
		Advertising or just speaking about other servers/commercial products will result in a permanent server ban;
		<info>This includes EVERY chat: mainchat, localchat, support chat, SMS, teamchat, carchat, etc;</info>
		<info>We can check logs, you have been warned;</info>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		It is not allowed to share hacks, cracks or illegal downloads on the server;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Bug abusing">
		It is not allowed to abuse any kind of bugs that give you an unfair advantage or spoil the fun of other players;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Blackmailing">
		Do not force/blackmail other players to do something they don't want to;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Non-english">
		The only language allowed in public channels is English (Main chat, team chat and support);
		<info>In the Local chat, Personal Messaging and Group chat, any language can be spoken;</info>
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Camping/spawn-arrest/kill">
		Camping at the hospital, Spawn-killing and Spawn arresting are forbidden;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Interfering with events">
		Arresting in a event is not allowed unless the event organizer says it's allowed;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Advertising in main chat">
		Do not use the mainchat for advertising your group or other services, use the /advert chat instead;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Spamming">
		Spamming chats is not allowed. Also, misusing the Support Channel will be punished with a mute;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Selling ingame content">
		Selling accounts or other in-game contents is not allowed;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Inappropiate name">
		You must use normal names. Names with spam, advertisement and inappropriate things are not allowed;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Trolling">
		Trolling other players is not allowed and is severely punished;
	</rule>
	<rule punish="Ignoring server staff">
		Always listen to server staff;
	</rule>
</rules>